[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why do travelers to La Paz, Bolivia, often become ill as soon as they arrive?", "correct_answer": "Because of the altitude", "incorrect_answers": ["Because of the high temperature", "Because of the humidity", "Because of the soil quality"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Jaws a mother puts a bounty on the great white shark, after her boy is killed. How much is the bounty?", "correct_answer": "$3,000", "incorrect_answers": ["$20,000", "$10,000", "$5,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What should humans do in order to keep planet Earth safe in the 1951 science fiction movie The Day the Earth Stood Still?", "correct_answer": "Curb their aggression", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Stop destroying the environment", "Become vegetarians"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor said Youre a very funny guy, Solly. I like you. Thats why I\u2019m going to kill you last.?", "correct_answer": "Arnold Schwartzenagger in Commando", "incorrect_answers": ["Carl Weathers in Predator", "Tom Berenger in Sniper", "Sean Connery in The Rock"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does gamophobia mean fear of marriage?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How is meat processed to produce the traditional South African dish called Biltong?", "correct_answer": "By curing", "incorrect_answers": ["By deep-frying", "By roasting", "By boiling"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Was Christina Applegate nominated for Best Female Performance for her role in the movie Dont Tell Mom the Babysitters Dead?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sourness is a taste that is a proof of which of the following properties of substances?", "correct_answer": "Acidity", "incorrect_answers": ["Temperature", "Toxicity", "Ionization"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1942 movie, Casablanca, who is the bartender at Ricks Caf\u00e9 Americain?", "correct_answer": "Sascha", "incorrect_answers": ["Pytor", "Karl", "Abdul"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When US President James Garfield was assassinated, this famous inventor tried to use his new metal detector to help the surgeons find the bullet.", "correct_answer": "Alexander G. Bell", "incorrect_answers": ["Nikolai Tesla", "Samuel F. B. Morse", "Thomas Alva Edison"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kelita Smith plays Delilah in the movie Dead Presidents.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of words does Rosie never use in the movie Princess Protection Program?", "correct_answer": "contractions", "incorrect_answers": ["four-letter word", "compounds", "proper nouns"]}]